topic: "<code>date</code> format strings"
deck: All::CS::Tools::date
notes:
-       guid: FMgE:]V,-h
        front: Day of week (1..7); 1 is Monday
        back: "`%u`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: Od+Nx=))6u
        front: Year (full)
        back: "`%Y`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: M81O~(U??T
        front: Last 2 digits of year
        back: "`%y`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: pHCfbWcmY3
        front: Alphanumeric TZ abbreviation
        back: "`%Z`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: bs|D6+R]nO
        front: "+hhmm numeric time zone (e.g., -0400)"
        back: "`%z`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: DXLLmoOXQ*
        front: "Time; same as %H:%M:%S"
        back: "`%T`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: c;LJ960I.R
        front: "Second (00..60)"
        back: "`%S`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: eH*DmQ2+Zg
        front: "Seconds since 1970-01-01 00:00:00 UTC"
        back: "`%s`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: MQ_8DvPaw6
        front: "24-hour hour and minute, same as %H:%M"
        back: "`%R`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: GImV809UYJ
        front: "Nanoseconds"
        back: "`%N`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: C-S|hk~RE)
        front: "Minute (00..59)"
        back: "`%M`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: K>`p%%D)`L
        front: "Month (01..12)"
        back: "`%m`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: e[ugu_K2}U
        front: "Hour (00..23)"
        back: "`%H`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: ut?)1L/sn]
        front: "Date; same as %m/%d/%y"
        back: "`%D`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: kZxKxur%m^
        front: "Day of month (e.g., 01)"
        back: "`%d`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: l8(EpB+,{)
        front: "Locale's date and time (e.g., Thu Mar  3 23:05:25 2005)"
        back: "`%c`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: p&M0]Ku@WT
        front: "Locale's full month name (e.g., January)"
        back: "`%B`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: Mfp3%!4*$H
        front: "Locale's abbreviated month name (e.g., Jan)"
        back: "`%b`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: Bn(Q(8@mKX
        front: "Locale's full weekday name (e.g., Sunday)"
        back: "`%A`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: kA}i5UWi1=
        front: "Locale's abbreviated weekday name (e.g., Sun)"
        back: "`%a`"
        include_reverse: true
-       guid: t?mJ.p@Q{#
        front: "A literal %"
        back: "`%%`"
        include_reverse: true
